Guide to the Marilyn Skolnick Papers, 1952-2009 AIS.2001.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Environmental Issues, 1970-2002; I.
  - SPRAWL, 1980-2001; 23.
    - 1998 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - 1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - 1999-2001 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - 2001 (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
    - SPRAWL Email Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - SPRAWL Email Correspondence, Inquirer Article, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - SPRAWL News clippings, 1994-1999 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - SPRAWL News clippings, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Transportation, 1991-1999; 24.
    The materialss in the Transportation subseries date from 1991 to 1999 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Environmental, 1991-1994 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Environmental, 1991-1996 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Environmental Issues, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Environmental Needs (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Forum, Transportation for Livable Communities, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Hill District Consensus Group, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - ISTEA, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Inspections, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Modeling, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Report, Transportation and Environment Task Force, undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Transportation Research Board, AD HOC Committee, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - US DOT Memo, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Urban Development, 1984-2001; 25.
    The documents in this subseries date from 1984 to 2001 and are arranged alphabetically by year and then alphabetically by subject.
    - 1992-2001 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - 1996-2001 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Allegheny County, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Brownfields Financial Redevelopment, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation Bulletin, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - News clippings, 1990-1997 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Joint Senate and House on Urban Affairs, Comments, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Joint Senate and House Committee on Urban Affairs, Testimony, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Urban America, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Urban Environment Committee, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Urban Land Institute, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Urban Land Institute, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Urban Redevelopment Authority, Bulletin, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Urban Redevelopment Authority, Environmental Issue, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Urban Zoning Code Project, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Water, 1987-2001; 26.
    The documents in the Water subseries date from 1987 to 2001 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - American Water Resources Association, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - American Water Resources Association, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation Bay Watcher, 1988-1990 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Clean Water Action, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Clean Water Action, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Clean Water Action, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Commission for Environmental Cooperation, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Community and Environmental Defense Services, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Department of Environmental Resources, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Environmental Federation, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Flood Plains Management, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Fox Chapel Water Tank, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Friends of the Rivers, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Groundwater, 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Groundwater Policy News, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Journals, 1987-1992 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Journals, 1988-1990 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Journals, 1988-1993 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Journals, 1988-1998 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989-1996 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993-2000 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996-2001 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999-2001 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Nine Mile Run, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Nine Mile Run, 1997-1999 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Nine Mile Run, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 24-25)
    - Nine Mile Run, 1999-2001 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Nine Mile Run, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Nine Mile Run, Proposal, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - North Area Environmental Council, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Three Rivers Community Fund, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Three Rivers Environmental Awards, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Water Quality, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Water Quality, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Watershed Restoration, Growing Greener, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Wetlands, 1988-1995; 27.
    The documents in the Wetlands subseries date from 1988 to 1995 and are arranged alphabetically by syear and then alphabetically by subject.
    - 1988 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - 1991 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - 1992 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - ACHD, undated (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Articles, 1990-1995 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - DER, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Pennsylvania, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Wildlife, 1992-1995; 28.
    The documents in this subseries date from 1992 to 1995 and are arranged alphabetically by year and then alphabetically by subject.
    - 1995 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Gamelands Management, Deer Population Issues, 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Transportation, 1961-2004; II.
  This series reflects Skolnick's opinions on Pennsylvania transportation issues and her aim to change transportation through all possible routes. She acted through standing committees at the Port Authority of Allegheny County (PAT), the Allegheny County Transit Council (ACTC), American Public Transit Association (APTA), the Transportation Research Board (TRB), Citizens Against New Toll Roads (CANTA), and the Monroeville Planning Commission. Skolnick's participation in each of these organizations and committees was relevant to the alterations she made in the Pittsburgh transportation system. This series has a wealth of information regarding Skolnick's time as a board member of PAT. In addition, Skolnick was heavily involved with the controversy over the construction of the Mon/Fayette Highway.
  This series originally contained many bound publications. A large number of these publications were in relation to the Mon/Fayette Highway in Monroeville, Pa. These publications included, but were not limited to, alternative analysis, environmental impact statements, and progress reports. Other removals include research records from the Transportation Research Board. These include journals on the subjects of traffic patterns, transit systems, handicap access, and highway management improvement. In addition, Marilyn Skolnick had collected a large number of copies of transportation laws, as well as numerous copies of U.S. Senate and House Bills relating to transportation issues (ex. SB 528).
  This series is divided into thirteen subseries, which arranged by subject. The material in this series date from 1961 to 2004.
  - Allegheny County Transit Council, 1984-2002; 1.
    The documents in the Allegheny County Transit Council subseries date from 1984 to 2002 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 1984 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - 1987-1992 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - 1991 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 51-52)
    - 1998-2002 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - 1999 (Box 25, Folder 2-5)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - 1999-2001 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - 1999-2002 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - 2020 Forum, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - 2020 Forum, Hearing, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - 2020 Plan, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Agendas, 1987-1991 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Agendas, 1995-2000 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Applications for Membership, 1988-1994 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Applications for Membership, 1992-1995 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Budget, 1993-1999 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - By-laws, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - By-laws, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Committees, 1986-1995 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, Peter Longini, 1987-1990 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, PAT, 1993-1996 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Executive Board, Presentation, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Executive Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Executive Committee, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Meeting, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Meeting, East Liberty Parking Garage Committee, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Meeting, East Liberty Executive Committee, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Meetings, General Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Membership List, 1990-1993 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Membership List, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Membership List, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Memorandum, 1989-1995 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Memorandum, 1992-1995 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Memorandum, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Memorandum, Comments on Proposed FY2000 Service Standards, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Memorandum, Tabling of ACTC Request Strip District Service, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1986-1998 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, Hamar Garage Meeting, 2000-2002 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, Publications, 1997-2001 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Presentation, PAT to ACTC, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Proposals, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - American Public Transit Association, 1983-2002; 2.
    The documents in this subseries date from 1983 to 2002 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 1987 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - 1987 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - 1990 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - 1992-1997 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - 1992-2000 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - 1993 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - 1993-1996 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - 1994-2002 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - 1995 (Box 26, Folder 16-17)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - 1996-2000 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - 1997 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - 1998 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - 1999 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Annual Meetings, 1992-2001 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Annual Meeting, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Annual Meeting Registration List, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Board Members Seminar, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Citizen Participation, A1D04, Disability, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Economic Stimulus Proposal, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - East Liberty Division, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Finance, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Financial Managers, Annual Conference, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Fiscal Year Budget, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Issue Briefings, undated (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Legislative Action, Federal, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Legislative Conference, Congressional Issue Summaries, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Legislative Conference, PAMTA, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Legislative Conference, Summary of Hill Visit, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Letters, 1993-1996 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Manual, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Memorandum, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Miami Conference, Docket No. 93-4, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Newsletter, Passenger Transport, 1994-2001 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Newsletter, Public Transit, undated (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Notes, 1991-1994 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Pamphlets, 1991-2000 (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Papers, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Policy and Planning Committee, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Policy and Planning Committee, Meeting, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Policy and Planning Committee, Meeting, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Presentation, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Public Transit, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Public Transit, Government, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Report, Access to Work Task Force, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Senior Citizens and Disabled Riders, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Transit Information Program, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Transit Management Conference, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 7-8)
    - Transit Now, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - US DOT, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - General, 1977-2004; 3.
    The documents in the General subseries date from 1977 to 2004 and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 2025 Long Range Plan, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - AA/DEIS, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - AASHTC Report on Clean Air Act Amendments, 1990-1992 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Ad Hoc Committee, Research Board Environmental Activities, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Aggressive Drivers, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Air Quality Conformity, Pittsburgh Transportation Management, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Allegheny Conference on Community Development, 1982-1987 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Allegheny Conference on Community Development, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Allegheny County, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Allegheny County Board of Commissioners, Crows Run, 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Allegheny County Public Participation Panel, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Allegheny Department of Planning, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - American Trucking Associations versus USEPA, 1997-1999 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - AMTRAK, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Automated Highway System Project, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Aviation, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Bidding Problems, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Bonding, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Bus Rapid Transit, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Center for Urban Transportation Research, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Carnegie Centennial, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - CATO Institute, Critique, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Citizen Participation, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Citizens Advisory Committee, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Citizens Advisory Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Citizens Advisory Committee, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Citizens Advisory Committee, Transit History, 1983-1985 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Citizens Advisory Council Advisory Newsletter, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Citizens Advisory Council, Annual Report, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Citizens Advisory Panel, TIP, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Citizens Against New Toll Roads, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Clairton Sportsmen's Club versus Pennsylvania Turnpike, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Collective Bargaining Seminar, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Committees, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Community Advisory Panel, undated (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Conference, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Conference on Institutional Aspects on Transportation Planning, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Contra Costa Transportation Authority, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence, 1995-2001 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence, Robert Kochanowski, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - County News Special Report, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Delaware Valley Regional Planning Commission, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Department of Environmental Protection, undated (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - EIS Impact on Highways, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Erie, Pennsylvania, undated (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Federal Transit Administration, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - FHWA Review of the Urban Transportation Planning Process, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Forum, Congestion and Mobility, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Golden Mile Highway, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Highway Safety Conference, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Health Effects, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Highways, 1991-1998 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Highways, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Highway and Bridge Reports, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Highway Symposium, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Hill District Consensus Group, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - IIHS Transportation Accidents, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - In the News, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Intercity Rail Passenger Commission, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Keystone Association of Railroad Passengers, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Lancaster Area Transportation Study, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Liberty South, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Maglev, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Maglev, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Maglev, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Maglev, 2000-2002 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Mallory, Brad, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Metropolitan Planning, undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Metrovision, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Monroeville Area Magport Station, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Monroeville City Council, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Monroeville Traffic, 1989-1991 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Moon Township, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Municipality of Monroeville, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Municipality of Monroeville, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - National Association of Regional Councils, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - National Conference on Transportation and Environment, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - National Cooperative Highway Research Program, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - National Economic Crossroads Transportation Efficiency Act, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - National Research Council, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - National Transit Institute, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - National Transit Institute, Public Involvement Programs, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - National Transportation System, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - National Transportation System Initiative, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Newsletters, 1992-1999 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Newsletters, 1992-2001 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1993-1998 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Nine Mile Run, undated (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Ohio Transportation Engineering Conference, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Parkway West Study, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Pennsylvania, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Pennsylvania, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Pennsylvania Association of Municipal Transportation Authorities, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Pennsylvania Association of Municipal Transportation Authorities, 1989-1991 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Pennsylvania Association of Municipal Transportation Authorities, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Pennsylvania Association of Municipal Transportation Authorities, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 50-51)
    - Pennsylvania Association of Municipal Transportation Authorities, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 52-53)
    - Pennsylvania Economy League, Transportation Committee, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 54)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 55)
    - Pennsylvania Mass Transit, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 56)
    - Pennsylvania Mass Transit, 1993-1999 (Box 28, Folder 57)
    - Pennsylvania Mass Transit, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 58)
    - Pennsylvania Mass Transit, undated (Box 28, Folder 59)
    - Pennsylvania Policy Plan Action Agenda, undated (Box 28, Folder 60)
    - Pennsylvania Public Transportation Association, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 61)
    - Pennsylvania Rural Transit Systems, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 62)
    - Pennsylvania Turnpike Commission, 1990-1999 (Box 28, Folder 63)
    - Pennsylvania Turnpike Commission, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 64)
    - Pennsylvania Turnpike Commission, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 65)
    - Pennsylvania Turnpike Commission, Expansion, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 66)
    - Pennsylvania Turnpike Commission, News clippings, 1979-1986 (Box 28, Folder 67)
    - Pittsburgh Area Transit, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh, Community Downtown Planning Forum, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Department of City Planning, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Transportation Management Area, 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Planning Advisory Committee Members, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Planning Advisory Task Force, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Planning Commission, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Presentations for Public Transit, 1990-2001 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Press Conference, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Privatization, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Program Status of Major Projects, 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Public Involvement, Evaluation Survey, 1993-1998 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Public Involvement, Making Public Involvement Work, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Public Involvement, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Public Involvement, Strategies in Transportation Planning, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Public Transportation, 1993-1998 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Public Transportation, Fiscal Review Task Force, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Public Transportation, Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Public Transportation Network, 1977-1984 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Public Transportation in Pennsylvania, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Publications, 1992-1996 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Purchase of Service Program, undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Railroad Electrification, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Regional Transportation, 1989-1993 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Regional Transportation District, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Review, 1994-1997 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Right of Way Task Force, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Route 28 Interchange, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Route 220 Improvement Project, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Sante Fe Transportation Workshop, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Seattle, Bellevue Transportation Management Association, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Shared Ride Program, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Southeastern Pennsylvania Transportation Authority Minutes, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Southern Beltway Transportation Projects, 1991-1994 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Southern Beltway Transportation Projects, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Southern Expressway, Petitions, undated (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Southwestern Pennsylvania Commission Schedule, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Southwestern Pennsylvania Growth Alliance, Legislative, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Southwestern Pennsylvania, Long Range Transportation Strategy, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Southwestern Pennsylvania Transit Association, 1990-1992 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Southwestern Pennsylvania Transit Coalition, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Southwestern Pennsylvania Transit Coalition for Transportation Act, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Speedlines, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - STAPPA/ALAPCO Alternative, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - State Enterprise Development Program Impact Report, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - State Studies on Transportation Planning, 1992-1999 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - State Transportation Advisory Committee, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - State Transportation Advisory Committee, 1984-1991 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - State Transportation Advisory Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - State Transportation Advisory Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - State Transportation Advisory Committee, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - State Transportation Advisory Committee, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - State Transportation Advisory Committee, Agenda, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - State Transportation Advisory Committee, Executive Summary, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 4)